ext.net 2017-12-04

# Privacy » Ext.NET

Ext.NET, Inc., and its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively “Ext.NET”) recognize the importance  
of keeping the personal information you provide to us private and secure. Ext.NET has developed a  
comprehensive privacy policy and we use the latest technology to ensure that your personal  
information is secure.

## Information Collection & Use

### General

We collect personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on  
our website. Any personal, private information you provide to us will be used in connection  
to contact you about the products or services in which you have expressed an interest or  
which may be related. We do not share any information about you or your company to  
unaffiliated third parties, except as necessary to administer the communications we offer  
and as permitted by law. We may use a third party service provider to for communications;  
that company is prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for  
any other purpose. If you follow us on Twitter, Facebook or on other social media services,  
we may use information provided by these services to customize our communications to you.  
We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide with other third  
parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

* * *

### Forums

In order to use our forums, you must first complete the registration form and create a user  
name and password. During registration you are required to provide contact information  
(such as name and email address). We may use this information to contact you about the  
products or services on our site in which you have expressed interest or which may be  
related. You may have the option to provide additional demographic information (such as  
title, company size, income level, gender etc.) to us; we encourage you to submit this  
information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site and in our  
marketing communications.

* * *

### Orders

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable  
information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name,  
email, and address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).  
We use this information for billing purposes and to fulfil your order. If we have trouble  
processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. We may also use this  
information to contact you about the products or services on our site which you have  
purchased or which may be related including information related to renewing your support  
subscription.

* * *

### Surveys or Contests

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on  
our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information  
from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you  
therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested  
information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and  
demographic information (such as zip code). We use this information to better understand our  
customers and to tailor any information that we may send you relating to our product or  
services. By participating in a contest, you give us permission to publicize your name and  
company affiliation solely in connection with the contest.

* * *

## Communications from the Site

### Special Offers and Updates

We will occasionally send you information on our products, services, special deals, or  
promotions. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these  
types of communications. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.

* * *

### Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to  
send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to  
unsubscribe. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.

* * *

### Service-related Announcements

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary  
to do so. For instance, if our forums are temporarily suspended for maintenance, we may send  
you an email notification.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.  
Please see “Choice and Opt-out.”

* * *

### Customer Service

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we may send you a welcoming  
email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response  
to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will  
communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

* * *

### Profile

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and third party  
tracking services such as Google Analytics to create a “profile” of your preferences.  
We may tie your personally identifiable information and your purchasing history, to  
information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers  
and to improve the content of the site for you. We do not share your profile with other  
third parties.

* * *

### Supplementation of Information

In order to provide certain services to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal  
information you submitted to us with information from third party sources.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

### Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We may share aggregated demographic and survey information about our user base with our  
partners. This information does not identify individual users. We do not link aggregate  
user data with personally identifiable information.

* * *

### Agents

We use a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies  
do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

* * *

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law  
and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with  
a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

* * *

### Choice/Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information  
used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase  
a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you  
can indicate your preference on our order form. If you no longer wish to receive our  
newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following  
the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at  
newsletter@ext.net.

* * *

### Log Files

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log  
files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet  
service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and  
clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to  
analyze trends, to identify defects, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around  
the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. IP addresses  
may be tied to personally identifiable information to identify your location or similar  
characteristics. We use a third-party tracking service that may use cookies, log files,  
or other technologies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to  
our site in the aggregate.

* * *

### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes.  
We use cookies on this site. We may link the information we store in cookies to any  
personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We may use both session  
ID cookies and persistent cookies. We may use session cookies to make it easier for you to  
navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent  
cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent  
cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. If you  
reject cookies, you may still use our site. Some of our business partners (e.g., our analytics  
provider) may use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.  
This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by us only and does not cover the use of  
cookies by any such firm.

* * *

### Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

We may employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help  
us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs  
are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to  
track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s  
computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size  
of the period at the end of this sentence. We may tie the information gathered by clear gifs  
to our customers’ personally identifiable information. We use clear gifs in our HTML-based  
emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge  
the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.  
If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see “Choice and Opt-out.”

* * *

### Links to Other Sites

This website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Ext.NET, Inc.  
Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.  
We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of  
each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy  
statement applies only to information collected by this website.

* * *

### Forums

If you use our Forums, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you  
submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be  
used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable  
information you choose to submit in these forums. Although the administrators and moderators  
of Ext.NET Forums will attempt to keep all objectionable messages off, it is impossible for  
us to review all messages. All messages express the views of the author, and neither the  
owners of Ext.NET Forums, nor vBulletin Solutions, Inc. (developers of vBulletin) will be  
held responsible for the content of any message. As a member of the Ext.NET Forums, you  
warrant that you will not post any messages that are obscene, vulgar, sexually-oriented,  
hateful, threatening, or otherwise violate any laws. We reserve the right to remove, edit,  
move or close any content item for any reason.

* * *

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted  
industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during  
transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method  
of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially  
acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute  
security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can send email us  
at privacy@ext.net.

* * *

### Business Transitions

In the event Ext.NET, Inc., goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition  
by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable  
information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent  
notice on our website of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

* * *

### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement,  
and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect,  
how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to  
modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material  
changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our  
home page.

* * *

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at  
[privacy@ext.net](mailto:privacy@ext.net).
